Hey, guys,
guess what?
What?
I know it's
last minute
but we've decided to
have a Halloween party.
Oh, good.
Great.
And everybody has
to wear costumes.
( all disagreeing )
Come on, it'll be fun.
Well, I'll be there.
I mean, I have to wear a costume
to all of my classes
that day anyway, so...
Please tell me you're
not going to dress up
like a dinosaur.
Not two years in a row.
I'll come to the party,
but I'm not dressing up.
You have to.
No way.
Look, Halloween is so stupid.
Dressing up and pretending
to be someone you're not?
You're an actor.
So, Ross, are you
going to bring Mona?
Yeah, yeah, I think I will.
The hot girl from their wedding?
Yeah.
Well, hey, if she needs
any ideas for costumes
she could be a bikini model
or a slutty nurse
or a sexy cheerleader.
Or, ooh, ooh, Leatherface
from Texas Chain Saw Massacre.
No, no, no.
Slutty Leatherface.
Wasn't Joey hitting on
her at the wedding, too?
That's right.
He was hitting
on her.
And I got her.
I guess the better man won.
Please don't
take her from me.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Oh. Ursula.
Oh.
Wait. It's...
it's me-- Phoebe.
Oh. I thought there
was a mirror there.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Wait a second now.
Um, so what's new with you?
Um, nothing.
I mean, I'm getting
married next week.
What?
Yeah, yeah. It's going
to be a small ceremony.
Just family.
His.
Huh.
Okay.
Well, I'm really
happy for you.
Wait.
If...
If you want to come,
I guess that'd be okay.
Really?
Sure. Why not?
You could be my
"sister" for the day.
Yeah. Okay.
Um, you know,
my friends are having
a Halloween party tonight
at my old apartment,
so you could come.
Maybe I could meet
the guy you're marrying.
Huh. Well, I'm
supposed to be working
at the restaurant tonight.
I'm supposed to be
working right now.
So, who cares?
Okay.
By the way, it's
a costume party.
Oh, okay, so that's
why you're...
No.
But thanks.
Hi.
Wait. You're supposed
to wear a costume.
I am.
I am a woman who spent
a lot of money on a dress
and she wants to wear it
because soon she won't
be able to fit into it.
Oh, I'm Catwoman...
who wants to
borrow the dress
when you're too big for it.
Okay.
( knock at door )
CHILDREN:
Trick or treat.
Oh, oh, can I
give out the candy?
I really want to be
with the kids right now.
Ever since I got pregnant
I have the strongest
maternal instincts.
CHILDREN:
Trick or treat!
( yelling ):
Just a minute!
( gasps )
Look at you guys!
Wow. You are a very scary witch.
And you are
a very funny clown.
And you...
are so in style right now.
You know
I work at Ralph Lauren
and the whole fall line
has got this, like,
equestrian theme going on.
I don't suppose you saw
the cover of British Vogue...
Can I just have a candy?
Yeah.
Sure.
Ah, Catwoman, so we meet again.
So we do, Supergirl.
It's me, Phoebe.
Monica, can I talk
to you for a second?
Listen, I appreciate you
getting me the costume.
You did this to him?
What?
I thought he'd love it.
His favorite kid's book
was The Velveteen Rabbit.
The Velveteen Rabbit
was brown and white.
Well, it was either
a pink bunny
or no bunny at all.
No bunny at all.
Always no bunny at all!
Hey.
You didn't
dress up, either?
Yes, I did.
I'm Chandler.
Dude, what happened?
How is that me?
CHANDLER:
Okay.
( clears throat )
I'm Chandler.
( whines loudly )
Oh, that is so you!
When have I
ever done that?
When have I ever done that?
( whines loudly )
( knock at door )
GIRL:
Trick or treat.
Oh!
Oh, well, you're just
the prettiest ballerina
I've ever seen.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
That deserves another
piece of candy.
Thank you.
( laughs )
Well, I have to
say that earns
"tutu" pieces of candy.
I love you.
Oh, oh!
Aw...
Oh, honey, here,
take it all.
Monica, we need more candy.
What? There's only
been, like, four kids.
Yeah, I know, but one of them
just said that she loved me
so I just gave her everything.
No wonder you're pregnant.
Hey.
What are you
supposed to be?
Remember
the Russian satellite Sputnik?
Well, I'm a potato
or a "spud"
and these are my antennae.
So, Sputnik becomes...
Spudnik! Spudnik.
Wow. I don't have
the worst costume anymore.
Hey, all right!
Ross came as Doody.
No, I'm not Doody.
No. Space Doody.
God!
Hey, sweetie.
Oh.
Aren't you going
to give me a kiss?
Okay, I will,
but right after
you have to tell me
who the hell you are.
Ursula?
Ursula's fiancée.
Oh, my God,
you're the sister.
Yeah.
Okay, I just slapped
my future sister-in-law's ass.
Yeah.
I'm an idiot.
Is you're mother here?
Maybe I can give her
a little slap on the butt.
My mother killed herself.
See, and I knew
that and...
now I'm sweating.
Look, look at me--
I'm really sweating.
I mean, now I'm saying:
Look at me-- I'm
getting even sweatier.
I think I should
probably just go.
No, that's okay.
We'll just start over.
Okay, hi, I'm Phoebe.
Uh, Eric.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Because the sweat's in my eyes
and it's burning.
Thank you.
There.
So what are you?
I don't think
they have a name for it.
I get nervous and I start
sweating like crazy.
No, I meant
your costume.
Oh, I'm...
I'm a solar system.
My students helped me make it.
I teach the second grade.
I love the second grade!
Really?
Yeah. It's so much
better than first grade
where you don't know
what's going on
and definitely better
than third grade
you know, with all
the politics and
the mind games and...
So, what do you do?
Um, I'm a masseuse... by day.
Good.
You don't have
to stand here with me.
No, I'm having fun.
And I'm really,
really excited
for you and Ursula.
I feel very lucky. She's great.
I think she's the most
beautiful woman I've ever seen.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Hey, Joey.
You read comic books, right?
Exclusively.
Who do you think
would win in a fight,
Catwoman or Supergirl?
Catwoman, hands down.
Yeah.
But between you and Phoebe
I'd have to give
the edge to Phoebe.
What? Really?
Are you kidding?
Phoebe lived
on the street, okay?
Plus she's got
this crazy temper.
She... she's not standing
right behind me, is she?
No. You're fine.
Do you think I
could take Rachel?
I'm not sure.
What?!
Come on! I am tough!
Punch right here
as hard as you can!
Okay, will you...
Will you relax?
What are you taking this
so seriously for?
It doesn't matter.
Oh, really?
Okay. What would you
say if I told you
that I thought
Ross or Chandler
could beat you up?
I would say,
"Woman, please."
Hey, Ursula's fiancée
is really sweet.
He's a teacher;
he does all this volunteer work.
You know, normally, you know,
I don't like really sweaty guys
but this one I could
just mop him up.
Oh, my God, Phoebe.
What?
You're getting a crush
on your sister's fiancée.
No, I'm not. You are!
Here comes the temper.
( knock at door )
Trick or treat.
Hi. You know what?
We're actually out
of candy right now
but someone just went out
to get some
and I... have been giving out
money, but I'm out of that, too.
Hey, can I write you a check?
Okay.
What's your name?
Leilani Meeholanofavich.
Okay, I'm just going to
write this out to cash.
Okay?
Hi, Mona.
Hey.
Hi.
Oh, hey.
Joey's going to be thrilled.
He was hoping you'd come by
as a slutty nurse.
Um, actually,
I'm just a nurse.
You'd think that
would embarrass me
but you see, I'm maxed out.
MONA:
Hi.
Hey, you made it.
Wait, wait. You're, um...
you're a potato.
Well, I'm a spud...
And the antennae...
Oh, my God, you're Sputnik!
Yes!
Marry her.
Okay, here's
a good one for you.
Who do you think
would win in a fight
between Ross and Chandler?
I can't answer that--
Chandler is my husband.
So, Ross?
Yeah.
Hey, beautiful.
Hello, handsome.
Oh, God.
Oh, look at you two.
So, when did
you guys meet?
Two weeks ago.
Two weeks, that's it?
Yeah, I know it sounds crazy
and it's not like me
to do something so impulsive
but she's just so perfect,
and we have so much in common.
Oh, really?
We're both teachers.
Huh?
And we were both
in the Peace Corps.
Peace Corps, really?
In fact, when we were
building houses in Uruguay
we were just two towns apart
and we never met.
Yeah. It wasn't a town
when I got there
but it was a town
when I left.
Shall we get me
really drunk?
Sure.
( forced chuckle )
Howdy, Doody.
That's funny, yeah.
You know, you're
the funniest man here
in a pink bunny costume
his wife made him wear.
Relax, man, relax.
You're looking
a little flushed.
I think we
might find out
the answer
to our question.
What question?
Monica and I were
talking about
who could kick whose ass
in a fight, you or Ross.
There's no question.
So you think Ross, too?
You picked Ross?!
Ross is really strong.
He's the strongest out
of all three of you
except for Joey.
I cannot believe
you didn't pick me.
In her defense,
she's right.
I am stronger;
I would destroy you.
Oh, really? You think
you're stronger?
Why don't you prove it?
Oh, I'll prove it!
I'll prove it
like a theorem!
MONICA:
Wait, wait, wait!
Okay, stop it!
Stop it! Stop!
Now, no one's going to fight
in this apartment!
Hey, Monica, people
came to see a fight.
Let's give them
what they came for.
Yeah!
You guys could arm wrestle.
Yeah, listen
to the slutty nurse.
You're going down.
You're going further down--
downtown!
Seriously, guys,
the trash talk is embarrassing.
Oh, Gunther,
you brought candy.
Thank you so much
for picking this up.
You are so sweet.
Really?
Yeah.
Someday you are going
to make some man
the luckiest guy in the world.
( knock at door )
Got to go.
BOY:
Trick or treat.
Hi!
Wow.
There you go.
My friend Louis told me
you were giving out money.
Oh, yeah, well, we were,
but now we've got candy.
I'd rather have the money.
Well, that-that's
not your choice.
Happy Halloween.
This isn't fair.
Well, is it fair that all
you did was put on a cape
and I got to give
you free stuff?
Shut up.
You shut up.
You can't tell me to shut up.
Uh... I think I just did
and, uh-oh, here it
comes again: Shut up.
Uh, Rache.
Yeah. I got it.
I'm good. I got it.
Now, wait a minute,
I had one more thing
I had to say to you:
Oh, right. Shut up.
You're a mean old woman.
Oh, wait. No. Shut up--
I mean, don't cry.
Let me get my checkbook.
Look, honey, you don't
have to do this, okay?
It's the strength
you have inside
that means
the most to me.
I mean, you're loyal
and you're honest
and you have integrity.
That's the kind of strength
I want in the man I love.
That means nothing to me.
Come on!
Aah.
Hi, liar.
Hey.
You know...
the only reason
he's marrying you
is because he thinks
all the things
you were saying
about yourself were true.
Well, they could be true.
But they're not.
Yeah. It's a
fine line, huh?
Why are you lying to him?
I don't know.
He said he did
all this stuff
and then I said
I did it, too
and he got so excited,
it was really fun.
Honey?
It's a filthy,
disgusting habit
and I want you
to quit now.
She's helped so many
people quit smoking.
You know, we really
better get going.
You have a church
group meeting tonight.
Right.
Well, it was nice
meeting you.
You, too.
And, Ursula, it was really nice
meeting you tonight!
Phebes, come on.
Bunny versus Doody.
We're waiting.
Okay. Okay, guys.
One match, winner take all.
Wait, wait.
What does the winner get?
Pride.
And dignity.
Okay, if you say so.
All right, ready?
Set, go.
( crowd cheering )
Doody! Bunny!
Wow, they're both
really strong.
Or equally weak.
Oh, my God.
Chandler's making
his sex face.
So, are you getting tired?
Nope. I can do this all day.
Yeah, me, too.
I'm getting a
little tired, though.
God, I'm exhausted.
Look, this is starting
to look really bad for me.
Okay, Mona... Mona's standing
right over there.
Oh, God, she's
talking to Joey.
You got to let me win.
Wait, if anything,
you've to let me win.
My wife thinks I'm a wimp.
Hey, at least you have a wife.
I keep getting divorces
and knocking people up.
And I'm dressed as Doody.
You're Spudnik.
Come on,
who are we kidding?
I'm Doody.
Please, she's watching.
( sighs )
Fine.
( grunts loudly )
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah!
Yay!
My hero.
You're a weird lady.
Hey, Ursula said
she left her purse.
Oh.
Oh, what a relief.
It has all the numbers of
the people in the prayer chain.
Sure it does. Yeah, yeah.
Well, I guess
I'll see you at the wedding.
Um, listen, I
don't think...
I don't think I'm going to
make it to the wedding, so...
I just want to wish you
all the luck in the world.
I think we'll be okay.
Besides, it's so perfect and...
( whispering ):
she's been saving
herself for me.
Okay, I can't
let you do this.
She's lying to you.
What?
She is lying, and I
bet I can prove it.
Excuse me.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah. Not a
prayer chain
but what looks like
a detailed drawing
of a bank floor plan.
Okay, here's
the name tag
from the restaurant
where she works
as a waitress.
Not a teacher,
a waitress.
All right, here's
her driver's license.
This ought to be good.
She always lies
about this.
How old did she
say she was?
She told me she was 25.
Oh. I almost don't
want to show you this.
Just remember, I'm
a minute younger.
I am so stupid.
Of course she was lying.
She's not a teacher.
There's no such thing as
the top secret elementary school
for the children of spies.
No, you're not,
you're not stupid.
I'm not smart.
I just wanted so much
to be impulsive for once.
To be romantic.
That's good.
You should
be impulsive
and you should
be romantic.
Just... you did it
with the wrong person.
What?
It's so weird, two people look
so much alike... so different.
Eric, let's go!
I better go deal.
Yeah, you should.
Hurry up!
I got to pray!
Hey.
Well, I had to give the kid
50 bucks to stop crying.
Well, that's not so bad.
I also had to go
to a couple houses with him
as his girlfriend.
Oh, I'm just awful
with children.
Come on. You're
good with kids.
They're just crazy
on Halloween.
You know,
they're all greedy
and hopped up on sugar.
Really? You think
that's all it is?
Absolutely. Halloween
is the worst.
Except for Christmas.
And their birthdays.
Mm-hmm.
They kind of get
a little crazy
during the summer, too.
And any time they're
hungry or sleepy.
Yeah, kids are tough.
Good luck with that.
Look, I wanted to tell you,
I'm, I'm sorry you lost.
Oh. Listen, I got a secret
for you: I let him win.
Is that a secret
or a lie?
No, I let him... Ross.
Would you tell her
that I let you win, please?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, Chandler "let" me win.
No, Chandler's really strong.
Oh, my arm is so sore.
Oh, nurse!
I am strong.
I'll show you.
Chandler, please.
Oh, what's the matter?
Are you scared?
Let's go, Big Bunny!
One, two, three. Go.
I'm going to kill myself.